adgaterewards.com 2019-01-07

# AdGate Media - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the use of adgatemedia.com.

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site. 

**Log Files and Cookies**

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site. 

adgatemedia.com engages in Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA) in accordance with the guidelines set forth by the Digital Advertising Alliance. AdGate Media uses anonymous cookies to track information on your browsing history on adgatemedia.com, and third-party advertising networks use the information to serve ads to you on AdGate Media's behalf on other sites throughout the Internet. These cookies do not contain personally identifiable information, nor are they linked to any personal information collected by AdGate Media.

You may opt-out of third-party advertising networks by using the Network Advertising Initiative's (NAI's) multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. These opt-outs are valid only for the computer and browser combination used to opt-out. Clearing cookies will remove these opt-outs since they stored in cookies.

If you opt-out of an NAI third-party advertising network, you will no longer receive ads based on your browsing history from that network. You may, however, continue to receive generalized online advertising. 

**Links to Other Websites**

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

**Registration and Use of Personal Information**

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing us at support@adgatemedia.com. You may also complete any corrections, updates or deletion requests at http://aff.adgatemedia.com/affiliates; you also may make your request by phone or postal mail at the address/phone number indicated at the end of this privacy policy.

**Security**

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. 

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at support@adgatemedia.com

**Links to Other Websites**

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

**Contact Details**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone or postal mail, our contact information is as follows:

support@adgatemedia.com

241 W 37th St  
Suite 1207  
New York, New York 10018 

This privacy policy was last updated on February 15, 2013.
